

#### **PROFILE**

I am a communicative and studious 28 year old woman with a calm and caring personality.

Last year I moved to the Netherlands and not long after decided to change my career to a more fulfilling field. I started studying Web Development; I aspire to become a Front-End Developer with a strong knowledge of UX as well.

I strive to deliver clear and accurate projects and also go the extra mile to really understand the content I'm working on. I enjoy creative problem solving processes and seeing pieces come together to form a satisfactory output.

Outside of work I like spending time in nature, travelling, music and reading. I am fond of learning languages and I am currently studying Dutch.

#### **CONTACT**

PHONE:

+31 62 202 29 17

**EMAIL** 

pulaylilla@gmail.com

#### **INTERESTS**

Languages IT Music Nature

# **LANGUAGES**

Hungarian (Native)
English (Professional working proficiency)
German (Elementary proficiency)
Norwegian (Elementary proficiency)
Dutch (Elementary proficiency)

# LILLA PULAY

Name: Lilla Pulay, dr.

Place of Residence: Lelystad, Netherlands Date of Birth: 18th November 1991

Gender: Female
Nationality: Hungarian
Driver license: Full Car

# **EDUCATION**

#### CareerFoundry

2020

#### **Full-Stack Web Development**

Expected date of completion: July 2020

# Károli Gáspár University - Faculty of Law

2011 - 2017 **Jurist (MA)** 

Qualification of diploma: Cum Laude

# Károli Gáspár University - Faculty of Law

2013 - 2016

#### **International Relations Expert (BA)**

Specialisation: International Economic Relations

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Booking.com

#### **Customer Service Guest Specialist**

May 2019 - November 2019

Assisting customers with their requests by handling phone calls, emails and messages and using various online tools as part of a multilingual team in a fast-paced environment.

#### **Deloitte Hungary**

# Tax Consultant, Global Innovation and Investment Incentives (Gi3)

September 2018 - March 2019

Analysing subsidy opportunities and R&D activities of companies, preparing and translating client presentations, supporting business development and scoping potential new clients, research and office administration.

# Budapest Metropolitan Police Headquarters (BRFK) Administrator, AETR

October 2017 - September 2018

Administrative tasks, contacting clients, drafting decision proposals and keeping track of the changes in relevant legal regulation.

# Dr. Zsombor Ercsey, Attorney at Law Intern (International Taxation Law)

March 2016

Legal research regarding various tax systems, international taxation, administrative tasks, office routine, drafting and translating emails for clients.

# IV and XV District Court of Budapest

**Intern (Criminal Department)** August 2015 – September 2015

Getting acquainted with court administration, legal research, participating in court hearings and drafting verdicts.

# Dr. András Somos, Attorney at Law Intern (Criminal law)

March 2015 - April 2015

Contacting clients, administrative tasks, office routine and drafting documents for clients and administrative bodies.

To whom it may concern,

Lilla Pulay has been working at Deloitte between 09/2018-03/2019 in the Grants and Incentives / Government Advisory team under my supervision.

Working with Lilla I got to know an enthusiastic, hard-working and committed teamplayer. She has an eye for the detail and delivers her work with a very structured output. She is always aiming for the best possible performance. She knows her strengths and development areas and is focused on self improvement; likewise, she is always open to feedback and acts upon it.

A key project we worked on together was an economy whitening study, which involved the analysis of the recent Government measures in Hungary, a thorough international benchmark on specific measures to support the cashless economy, and an in-depth analysis of economic areas with the highest potential of whitening in Hungary (i.e. construction sector, car retail and reparation, etc.). Besides writing the study numerous presentations were developed for project meetings and progress reports, both in Hungarian and English languages. Lilla also participated in client meetings and provided valuable input. Her commitment and structured & precise work was essential for the success of the project as other staff's availability was very limited during the project's course.

Our team was sad to learn that Lilla left us for -very understandable- personal reasons and we miss her in our team since. We hope that she will quickly find her path in her new journey.

Best Regards,

Bence Kovats

#### **Bence Kovats**

Manager | Public Sector Advisory Deloitte Co. Ltd. Dózsa György út 84/C, Budapest, H-1068, Hungary M: +36 (20) 365 6257 bkovats@deloittece.com | www.deloitte.hu